[
  {
    "prompt": "Hi (casual)",
    "answers": ["안녕"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hello (polite)",
    "answers": ["안녕하세요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Nice to meet you",
    "answers": ["만나서 반갑습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes (casual)",
    "answers": ["응"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah (casual)",
    "answers": ["어"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes (polite)",
    "answers": ["네"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes (formal)",
    "answers": ["예"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No (casual)",
    "answers": ["아니"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No (polite)",
    "answers": ["아니요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Good, I like it",
    "answers": ["좋습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't like it",
    "answers": ["싫습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know",
    "answers": ["모릅니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thanks (casual)",
    "answers": ["고마워"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thanks (polite)",
    "answers": ["고마워요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thank you (formal)",
    "answers": ["고맙습니다", "감사합니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sorry (casual)",
    "answers": ["미안해"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sorry (polite)",
    "answers": ["미안해요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sorry (formal)",
    "answers": ["죄송합니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No problem",
    "answers": ["아닙니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm okay",
    "answers": ["괜찮습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Excuse me",
    "answers": ["실례합니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Please",
    "answers": ["부탁합니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Give me",
    "answers": ["주세요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thanks for the meal (before)",
    "answers": ["잘 먹겠습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thanks for the meal (after)",
    "answers": ["잘 먹었습니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Goodbye (they go)",
    "answers": ["안녕히 가세요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Goodbye (they stay)",
    "answers": ["안녕히 계세요"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Happy birthday",
    "answers": ["생일 축하합니다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "This one",
    "answers": ["이것"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That one",
    "answers": ["저것"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mom (casual)",
    "answers": ["엄마"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mother (polite)",
    "answers": ["어머니"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dad (casual)",
    "answers": ["아빠"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Father (polite)",
    "answers": ["아버지"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Water",
    "answers": ["물"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Bus",
    "answers": ["버스"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Subway",
    "answers": ["지하철"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Taxi",
    "answers": ["택시"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Travel",
    "answers": ["여행"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Work",
    "answers": ["일"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Meal",
    "answers": ["밥"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Family",
    "answers": ["가족"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Grandmother",
    "answers": ["할머니"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I, me",
    "answers": ["나"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Older brother (male to male)",
    "answers": ["형"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Husband",
    "answers": ["남편"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Older sister (male to female)",
    "answers": ["누나"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Younger sibling",
    "answers": ["동생"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Daughter",
    "answers": ["딸"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Kid, child",
    "answers": ["아이"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We, our",
    "answers": ["우리"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Older sister (female to female)",
    "answers": ["언니"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We, our (honorific)",
    "answers": ["저희"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Older brother (female to male)",
    "answers": ["오빠"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Baby",
    "answers": ["아기"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wife",
    "answers": ["아내"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Son",
    "answers": ["아들"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Grandfather",
    "answers": ["할아버지"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Anxiety, worry",
    "answers": ["걱정"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Anger",
    "answers": ["화"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Feeling",
    "answers": ["기분"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Glad, happy",
    "answers": ["기쁘다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Embarrassed, ashamed",
    "answers": ["창피하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Surprised, amazed",
    "answers": ["놀라다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Happiness",
    "answers": ["행복"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Enjoyable, cheerful",
    "answers": ["즐겁다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Scary",
    "answers": ["무섭다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Envious",
    "answers": ["부럽다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Uneasiness, restlessness",
    "answers": ["불안"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Love",
    "answers": ["사랑"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Smile, Laugh",
    "answers": ["웃다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Cry",
    "answers": ["울다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sad",
    "answers": ["슬프다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Excited",
    "answers": ["신나다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Depressed",
    "answers": ["우울하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lonely",
    "answers": ["외롭다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Personality",
    "answers": ["성격"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Strong",
    "answers": ["강하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Activity",
    "answers": ["활동"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lie",
    "answers": ["거짓말"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fear",
    "answers": ["겁"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lazy",
    "answers": ["게으르다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Kindness",
    "answers": ["친절"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Joke",
    "answers": ["농담"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Different",
    "answers": ["다르다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Good-hearted",
    "answers": ["착하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Embarrassed, shy",
    "answers": ["부끄럽다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Diligent",
    "answers": ["부지런하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Unfriendly, unkind",
    "answers": ["불친절하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thought",
    "answers": ["생각"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hurry, rush",
    "answers": ["서두르다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Habit",
    "answers": ["습관"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Endure",
    "answers": ["참다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Popularity",
    "answers": ["인기"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Boast, brag",
    "answers": ["자랑"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Confidence",
    "answers": ["자신감"]
  }
]
